Condition this day and age, friendly face on every page
A laugh track floating through the haze
Everything feels safe these days
The neighbors wave, the children play
The sun shines bright, bills get paid
Stories tame, told the same
The mother grins, the ending always lets you win its role
Okay here we are so what's going on what ghost or is that uh
humana sorry if i got your name wrong so sorry ours another is another one ghost has messed up
with oh no i love i can put pieces together for your ghost i don't know oh because i'm having a
Here we are at spiritual apathy. I know I know he's difficult to deal with
I'm having a hard day
But if you want to card I was doing it readings earlier on LES this show and they love them
I mean, it's like I'm like, why don't I do more readings in my show like my
Like I think think that uh people like forgets that I like I'm pretty
Actually good at reading like uh, I read for somebody was his name is like my locker or something
But he's like well
Like that was really he's like, he's like somebody has told me like almost exactly what you said like almost had exactly how you said like it was like
There's something like some message coming to him, right? And so
So he was impressed and you know
Easy got me these really cool cards last year. They're like the hoodoo tarot cards. I'm sorry. I'm like I get a little stoned right now
It's a weird time of a year. It's it but it's almost the summer solstice is think like once the summer solstice hits like the energy
It's gonna go way up. I think it's always like a
Like a lull before like the the sun, you know, and it's like we're getting into those dog days of dog days of
July
So ghosts didn't come up. I think ghosts ran away. Okay, maybe you ran away, too
I don't know but I was watching that. I mean, oh, yeah, I was gonna play this one
To here
Oh come on gather around everybody gather around
Oh no Eliza you're not the one that he got in all the trouble over for you. I don't know if I can take into their scandal right now
Okay
No, okay. Oh, I know I wasn't really talking. I was playing the music I can pull some cards on it
Like I don't know. He just disappeared. I mean he disappeared
What I didn't hear you. Oh, I'm sorry. No, I said I said I said I'm just I said
Ghost is kind of crazy, but oh
I'll pull some cards. I said
So it's going up. Are you are you the girl that like, you know, he got in a little controversy over?
That's what I'm saying
Six of coins, this is like generosity
There's like you've been generous with somebody or you generous with him or somebody's been generous with you
Okay, there's a generosity card six of coins. It's almost like it's almost like give me to the right person
That's someone that needs it like you're able to figure that out
Also, you have the two of sticks. This is like finding some balance. This is like getting also your grounding in something right there
Don't think you know me too. Well, okay. I don't I don't think I've ever met you Eliza
I know ghost got me who a scandal you're a little bit me. Okay, but there's like some kind of balance also like he's like
He's kind of like looking first like it's like a what is it? His row boat or is like a steamboat or something to come in
You know, it's like he's like there's some kind of like
Steamboat or something like that. What's what is this? Is there something a gambling offshore or something? I don't know what's going on here
What are you up to ghosts? Oh, and I have to give this this kind of cubs. This is like a happiness
Yeah, ghost is Tyler. Ghost is Tyler that that Tyler ghost is Tyler's alter egos
We don't ten of baskets is a ton of cups. It's like a lot of happiness
You said Tyler. Okay. Yeah, okay. Well Tyler's gone
I don't know, I don't know, there's this girl,
there's this crazy mentally ill woman,
she's like 20 years old, I don't know what her name was,
but hey what's up white dog, how are you, good to see you?
But yeah, and then he got into a scandal
because he like, asked for her phone number
and they're like, oh well, she's like a retarded woman
and stuff, and then she called the police on him
or something, I don't know, there's a whole thing,
but I don't know, he just disappeared, he dipped,
he dipped out, what's up white dog, I don't know,
I really don't know about it, I don't know.
You know, you know him in real life. He thought he was coming into the chat. Yeah, he was just here. He asked for the link
You know in real life. What's he like in real life? Is he?
It's like flatulent. You don't know. We don't know my ghost. Oh, do you work with them?
It tells the tea. I like to know about the
True story of ghosts tell us a ghost story, you know, we can it's a horror theme show
Mm-hmm. I've been a white claw, but I'm almost done with it
I had a couple other drinks today too, but I was I drink really slowly today and
You know
He's messy abusive. Oh, I know he's he's been terrible to me. He's been terrible to me
No, he was very generous at one point and then it all dried up
He's making your life hell. I mean mine too mine too
We need just we need to like form a ghost support group
She has that guy. I mean
Oh my gosh, one thing after another with a ghost, right?
I gotta love him, gotta love him.
I have a song, have you ever seen the ghost song?
He knows you have PTSD, he's like that.
He's just like, if you can take advantage
of something, he will, especially if it's me.
I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
Let me see if I have a ghost till before us.
Let me see.
Have you ever heard of the ghost song, Eliza?
I wrote the song, which is just for ghosts.
We played it. I think I played it at last year's Halo ween. I think Halo was in the chat earlier too
Halo ween
Missed if I have the ghost sober song though. I don't see it coming up right away. I think I might have
Buried it. Oh there it is. I found it. You're ready for the ghost sober song. This usually was summoning
usually was summoning him out of like a
He's too drunk. He'll summon him out of his
Sleep you through to sing with the ghost song. Well, it's gonna come into your mind right now. You love that you love the song too
Eliza, you know, let's play it
Okay, you don't want to summon him but maybe he's gonna come when I play this. He'll definitely come. I have to play it though
Heroes and loud like thunder on caffeine drop stacks cracking jokes keep in the scene clean
The crowd starts house just grins
Let's get down
I was reading boy
May I have the mission to crush out
Coast already did it to the voice of the desert war brings it loud
Psyche he's proud proud they talk slick why is he still around
chose to believe most just lie and chose to leave me in a world full of clowns he's the
best to face when screaming me and burning paint to a digital flame may i have permission to crash out
this man to beat up who did what a bitch
dumb dumb to the ones who doubt ease your glass to the ghost girl
well ghost wanted to run to beat us i mean it's like okay i mean it's like
everyone's gonna go run to hers now okay go everyone go run to beat it's okay it's okay
if something from the past is still following you old patterns heavy energy or repeating obstacles
this is the moment the cycle begins to break everyone is the force beyond time he clears what